// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/en.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],


}



export var cards = {
  "Alpha": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Α</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Alpha"
  },
  "Beta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Β</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Beta"
  },
  "Gamma": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Γ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Gamma"
  },
  "Delta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Δ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Delta"
  },
  "Epsilon": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Ε</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Epsilon"
  },
  "Zeta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Ζ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Zeta"
  },
  "Eta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Η</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Eta"
  },
  "Theta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Θ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Theta"
  },
  "Iota": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Ι</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Iota"
  },
  "Kappa": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Κ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Kappa"
  },
  "Lambda": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Λ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Lambda"
  },
  "Mu": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Μ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Mu"
  },
  "Nu": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Ν</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Nu"
  },
  "Xi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Ξ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Xi"
  },
  "Omicron": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Ο</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Omicron"
  },
  "Pi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Π</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Pi"
  },
  "Rho": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Ρ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Rho"
  },
  "Sigma": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Σ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Sigma"
  },
  "Tau": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Τ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Tau"
  },
  "Upsilon": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Υ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Upsilon"
  },
  "Phi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Φ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Phi"
  },
  "Chi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Χ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Chi"
  },
  "Psi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Ψ</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Psi"
  },
  "Omega": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">Ω</div>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Omega"
  }
  
};